<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshop on Computational Models of Natural Argument (CMNA 20)</title>
    <link>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Workshop on Computational Models of Natural Argument (CMNA 20)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dates</title>
      <link>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/dates/</guid>
      <description> Key Dates  Regular Paper submission (long &amp;amp; Short papers): 1st July 2020 Notification to authors: 15th August 2020 Early registration deadline: See COMMA call for details Final (Camera Ready) version of papers: 31st August 2020 Workshop: 8th September 2020 Main COMMA Conference: 9th-11th September 2020  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/home/</guid>
      <description>Since its inception in 2001, the CMNA workshop series focuses on the issue of modelling “natural” argumentation, where naturalness may range across a variety of forms, perhaps involving the use of visual rather than linguistic means to illustrate a point, for example using graphics or multimedia, or applying more sophisticated rhetorical devices, interacting at various layers of abstraction, or exploiting “extra-rational” characteristics of the audience, taking into account emotions and affective factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organisation</title>
      <link>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/organisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/organisation/</guid>
      <description> If you have any questions or queries then feel free to contact a member of the organising committee
Organising Committee  Floriana Grasso floriana@liverpool.ac.uk University of Liverpool Nancy Green nlgreen@uncg.edu University of North Carolina Greensboro Jodi Schneider jschneider@pobox.com University of Illinois Urbana Champaign Simon Wells s.wells@napier.ac.uk School of Computing, Edinburgh Napier University  Programme Committee    --  Floriana Grasso University of Liverpool Nancy Green University of North Carolina Greensboro Jodi Schneider University of Illinois Urbana Champaign Simon Wells School of Computing, Edinburgh Napier University  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programme</title>
      <link>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/programme/</guid>
      <description>The programme for the day has yet to be finalised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission</title>
      <link>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/submission/</guid>
      <description>The workshop encourages submissions in four categories:
 Long papers, either reporting on completed work or offering a polemic discussion on a burning issue (up to 10 pages). Short papers describing work in progress (up to 5 pages). Demos (2 page abstract describing the demo) Posters (2 page abstract explaining the concept behind the poster).  It is highly recommended, but not mandatory, to format papers using the Springer LNCS format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topics</title>
      <link>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/topics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arg.napier.ac.uk/events/cmna/topics/</guid>
      <description>The workshop focuses on the issue of modelling &amp;ldquo;natural&amp;rdquo; argumentation. Contributions are solicited addressing, but not limited to, the following areas of interest:
 The characteristics of “natural” arguments (e.g. ontological aspects, cognitive issues, legal asepcts). The linguistic characteristics of natural argumentation, including discourse markers, sentence format, referring expressions, and style. The generation of natural argument Corpus argumentation results and techniques Argumentation mining Models of natural legal argument Rhetoric and affect: the role of emotions, personalities, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>